Narrator: Acronyms and initialisms
Common acronyms and initialisms
Narrator: 1
M: Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome
Narrator: 2
F: Also Known As
Narrator: 3
F: As Soon As Possible
Narrator: 4
M: Absent WithOut Leave
Narrator: 5
F: Chief Executive Officer
Narrator: 6
M: Do It Yourself
Narrator: 7
M: Date Of Birth
Narrator: 8
F: Estimated Time of Arrival
Narrator: 9
F: Frequently Asked Questions
Narrator: 10
M: For Your Information
Narrator: 11
F: Gross Domestic Product
Narrator: 12
M: Graphic Interchange Format
Narrator: 13
M: Greenwich Mean Time
Narrator: 14
F: Human Immunodeficiency Virus
Narrator: 15
F: Human Resources
Narrator: 16
M: Master of Business Administration
Narrator: 17
F: Member of Parliament
Narrator: 18
M: National Aeronautics and Space Administration
Narrator: 19
M: Personal Assistant
Narrator: 20
F: President Of The United States
Narrator: 21
F: Prisoner Of War
Narrator: 22
M: Public Relations
Narrator: 23
F: Sports Utility Vehicle
Narrator: 24
M: Unidentified Flying Object
Narrator: 25
M: Universal Serial Bus
Narrator: 26
F: Unique Selling Point